Previously on Desperate Housewives
前情提要
Dave!
大卫
Is that the bathroom?
洗手间在这里吗
No.I think that's it there.
不  应该在那边
Oh, okay.Thanks.
谢谢
Dave tried to eliminate a witness to murder
大卫试图诬陷证人为凶手
But Jackson survived...
杰克逊却死里逃生
I bought M.J. a fishing pole.
我给M.J.买了鱼竿
We're not gonna be able to make it this weekend.
恐怕这周不能去了
- I'm kind of getting married.
-我要结婚了
What?
什么
- I thought I heard you out here.
-我一下就听出你的声音了
Jackson.
杰克逊
Forcing him to change his plans.
他不得不另做打算
I'm a middle-aged guy...
我不年轻了
Tom was searching.
汤姆深感迷茫
And I don't know what I wanna do with my life.
我不知未来的人生之路如何寻觅
We're rich again! Hallelujah!
我们又有钱了  哈雷路亚
Gaby's life returned to normal.
加布重回富人行列
We're gonna be us again-- the old Carlos and Gaby.
我们又会像从前那样风光
I'm gonna make sure that you walk away from this marriage
我保证你毫无损失
With your assets intact. Now to accomplish this...
包括你的公司和财产  为了做到这一点
And Bree agreed to protect what she felt was hers.
布里同意保护本属于自己的财产
I'm capable of doing whatever needs to be done.
一切都听您部署
The lawyer arrived just after sundown.
夕阳斜下  律师现身
He checked to make sure no one was watching,
他确定没人跟踪他
then he hurried to the front door...
便很快来到门前
where his client was waiting.
他的客户  等候已久
As she poured him the scotch he requested,
为他斟上美酒之后
the client began to wonder
客户便开始咨询
exactly how he planned to hide her assets
他将如何保护她的财产
from the husband she was divorcing.
不受到离婚影响而缩水
The lawyer suggested some creative accounting.
律师提出伪造账目
His client agreed.
客户表示同意
He suggest a secret bank account.
他建议做秘帐
She agreed.
她点头赞成
He suggested a second set of books.
当他叙述备选方案时
She agreed.
她表示应允
And then the lawyer looked deep into his client's eyes
随后律师注视她眼神深处
and made one final suggestion...
作了最后的一个提议
that she was completely unprepared for.
大大出乎她的意料
You want me to rob my own house?!
你要我抢劫我的自己家
Not exactly. I was thinking hire my friend Tony to do it.
不完全是  我想请我的朋友汤尼来办
Absolutely not.
当然不行
I am all up for a little creative accounting
我已经同意做假账
and some secret bank accounts,
甚至做秘帐
but hiring some thug to stage a break-in?
何必要再请小丑来假装入室
It's a community property state, babe.
夫妻共有财产的分配是这个国家的法律
Orson's going to get half of everything,
奥森会拥有一半财产
including your jewelry, your artwork, your antiques.
包括你的珠宝  你的艺术品  还有古董
Wouldn't it be easier to just have him killed?
这么说干掉他会简单很多
As your lawyer, I can't condone that.
作为一个律师  我不赞成这么做
- That said, I have a cousin--
-不过我有一个表弟
I was kidding!
我是开玩笑的
So was I. Loosen up, freckles.
我也是啊  放松点  小可爱
Well, I just never know with you.
我太不了解你了
And don't call me "freckles."
还有别叫得这么肉麻
Look, if you're not comfortable with Tony,
如果你不放心汤尼办事
why don't we do the job ourselves?
我们也可以自己来啊
I bet you'd look hot in a ski mask.
我打赌你带上面具一定性感极了
You are repugnant,and this conversation is over.
可恶  谈话就到此为止吧
Fine, but since I'm charging you for the full hour,
好吧  不过基于我是按小时收费
let me make it worth your while.
为了让你觉得服务超值
Sit down and close your eyes.
闭眼坐下  听我道来
What? No!
什么  我不要
Just humor me. Come on.
来吧  逗我笑笑
Now I want you to picture Orson after the divorce.
现在想象离婚后的奥森
He owns half of your business, half of your assets.
拥有你一半的事业和资产
You see it?
能想像吗
Go on.
继续
Now I want you to picture Orson dating some young bimbo.
现在想一想他和一个骚娘们约会
And don't kid yourself.
大胆去想吧
He will get a bimbo.
他会找一个骚娘们的
Now picture your favorite strand of pearls
好  现在你最爱的珍珠项链
dangling in the 24-year-old cleavage of said bimbo
在一个24岁骚货的乳沟之间摆动
while she is using
她将你罗伯特 弗洛斯特的首版诗集
your first edition Robert Frost as a coaster...
用来当杯托
And your 19th century french crystal vase as an ashtray.
把你19世纪的法国水晶作烟灰缸
If you can live with that...I will leave.
如果你能忍受这些  我就放手
And with that,
于是
The client offered a suggestion of her own...
该客户终于下了决心
we should probably break a window to make look more real
如果破窗而入  现场才更真实
And the lawyer agreed.
律师同意了
更多字幕请访问 http://www.yyets.net/
本字幕由人人影视荣誉出品
校对：小门柴
翻译：桃金娘银 小天天鱼 Joanna Vicky 祭司
总监：小门柴
时间轴：小门柴  毛毛
Masks..you can find them in any home.
面具  每家每户都能找到
Some are used once a year to scare the neighbors...
有为增加节日气氛  吓唬邻居的
Some are needed for the occasional chore.
有的做家务时  能保护我们
Some are applied every other Thursday.
有的在周末前  能帮我们修护肌肤
Then there's the kind of mask
而有一种面具
some men wear every day.
有些人每天都会戴着
It's a friendly smile
那就是示好的微笑
designed to hide the most wicked of intentions.
它被用以掩饰邪恶的阴谋
Hey, M.J., is your mom home?
M.J你妈妈在家吗
She's inside talking to Jackson.
她和杰克逊在家里聊天
Really?
是吗
So... what do you think of Jackson?
你觉得杰克逊人怎么样
I like him. He buys me comic books.
我喜欢他 他常给我买连环画
Yeah, he's a good guy.
是啊  他是个好人
He was very brave that night
他在酒吧起火那晚
during that fire at the nightclub.
表现得很英勇
Does he ever talk about that fire?
他跟你提过火灾吗
Or anybody he saw that night?
提过那晚看到什么人吗
Has the police stopped by to ask him any questions?
警察来问过话了吗
- If they do, would you let me know?
-如果他们来了  告诉我
Why?
为什么
Well. I wanna make sure they are
我要保证他们
Being nice to our friend Jackson.
对杰克逊的态度是友善的
Because he is such a good guy.
他可是个好人
It is such a stunning piece.
多漂亮的花瓶啊
It is simple and elegant, don't you think?
简约  优雅  你不觉得吗
I mean, I know it was expensive.
我知道很贵
But you cannot put a price tag on beauty, am I right?
但美丽是不能用价格衡量的  对不对
So when daddy finds out how much I spent,
要被是你老爸发现了
would it be okay if I used you as a human shield?
你能不能帮我挡挡
You know, I should really get you tested
应该先试试你才行
- Mom.
-妈
Hi. Do you have fun playdate with Heather?
今天和希瑟玩得好吗
She's got a canopy bed. I want one
她有个四柱顶蓬床  我也想要一个
We just bought you a bed. It's not a year old
我们才给你买了新床  一年还不到呢
I don't like it anymore. I want sleep under a canopy
我不喜欢了  我想要在天蓬下睡觉
Then go move in with Heather,
那你去和希瑟一起去住吧
because I'm not getting you one.
因为我不会给你买
Why not? We are rich.
为什么不行  我们有钱啊
Who told you that.
谁跟你说的
I heard you telling Aunt Bree
我听见你和布里阿姨说话了
Since daddy got his new job, we are rolling in money.
爸爸有了新工作  我们就能日进斗金
Well, mom should not have said that
妈妈不应该这么说
When Aunt Bree started bragging about to her Prada bag,
但布里阿姨显摆她的普拉达包包
mommy kind of lost it
妈咪就有点忍不住了
Whatever, I want a canopy and you gotta get me one.
不管啦  我想要天蓬床  你必须给我买一个
I don't have to get you anything
我没必要满足你任何要求
and stop acting like a spoiled brat.
别像个宠坏的小孩似的
I am not spending a fortune on a bed you don't need.
我才不花钱去买没必要买的床
But you can spend millions of dollars on a stupid vase?
那你自己就能掷千金购入白痴的花瓶
That vase is not stupid.
这花瓶才不白痴呢
Is that vase stupid?
是不是很丑很白痴
You know what? This coversation is over. Go to your room.
谈话结束  回房间去
You too. Bubble head.
你也回去  点头娃娃
Ok. My clothes are in the closet.
好  我的衣服都在衣柜里了
And I am going to put my toothbrush in the bathroom
我现在把牙刷放到浴室去
Oh just leave the toilet seat up And the immigration
只要把马桶坐垫立着
people will totally think we are married.
移民局的人就会相信咱们结婚了
I don't know how I'm gonna thank you for doing this.
我不知道怎么感谢你为我做这么多
I do think of one way you could repay me.
我想出一件你能回报我的事情
- You got it.
-没问题
No. Not like that.
不  不是这种
No. I was thinking, after our quickie courthouse ceremony,
我只是想  我们仪式完了之后
you could buy me a cake.
你可以给我买个蛋糕
I love wedding cake,
我喜欢结婚蛋糕
It's the one part of marriage that never lets you down.
漂亮的蛋糕是每场婚礼必备的
I can do you better than that.
我能做的更好
- How about I throw us a big engagement party.
-不然我们搞个订婚聚会
What?
什么
We are not having wedding.
我们没举行结婚
and we're gonna need pictures of something
我们也需要一些照片
to put in our photo album as evidence.
整理成相册  作为证据
I guess that could be fun.
我猜一定很有意思
While our friends are toasting to our everlasting happiness,
当朋友们举杯祝咱们天长地久的时候
we can yell, "surprise! It's all a sham!
我们就喊出来  给你个惊喜  都是假的
Thanks for the crock-pot!"
谢谢你的炖锅
No. No. We can't tell anybody this is fake.
不不  我们不能告诉任何人这是假的
The whole thing could blow up.
所有事情会搞砸的
- Can I at least tell girls?
-能告诉我姐们吗
No way.
当然不行
I mean, they don't call her "gabby" for nothing.
长舌妇会来真的(Gabby暗指多嘴)
Fake marriages they are just complicated
假结婚还真是复杂啊
I know I am asking a lot, Susan.
我知道我要求太多了  苏珊
No. No. It's Ok. I want to do this.
不  没事  我想帮你
The truth is I miss you.
事实上  我也很想你
House has been kinda lonely since you left.
自从你离开之后  房子一直都很空
Well, I hear you loud and clear.
我听见了
Not that lonely.
不是这个意思
- What are you doing?
-你在这干什么
Thinking.
沉思
Well, think inside. I made pork chops.
到屋里沉思吧  我做了猪排
Are you gonna ask me about my job interview?
你不想问问我面试如何吗
Oh, right. How'd that go?
好  情况怎样
Okey. until the 30-old who was interviewing me asked me
很好  直到一个30岁的面试官问我
If I'd ever used twittering as part of market campaign.
是否用过Twitter来作为市场营销的战略
And what would you say.
那你说什么
Nothing. Because I don't know what twittering is.
无话可说  因为我什么都不知道
It's a social networking tool where you sent instant updates
这是社交互联工具  你可以发送即时信息
To anybody who signs up for them.
给所有登陆注册的人
So you knew about it. And yet you kept it from me?
你知道这个  还藏着没告诉我
I didn't keep it from you.
我没有不告诉你
It's just one of those tech things that you don't care about.
只是一些科技产品  你不太在意而已
It is for young people.
年轻人用的
I am a dinosaur marching into the tar pit.
反正我就是落伍
I didn't say that.
我可没这么说
You're not gonna get a whole lot of sympathy from me.
咱们同命相怜
I just went through the same thing, remember?
我也经历一样的事情  记得吗
But you didn't tell me how bad it was
你没说这有多糟
That is another thing you kept from me
这件事你也没跟我说
50 guys showed up for that one job.
50个人来抢这个职位
And I was ten years older than every single one of them
我要比他们任何一个人都老10岁
I could hear 'em twittering as I left the room.
我离开房间  我能听见他们在议论
I think you mean "tittering."
我想  你是想说偷笑你吧
Sorry. Please. Don't hit me.
抱歉  别揍我
I heard a door slam shut today, Lynette.
我今天感到一扇大门向我关上了  勒奈特
It's official. My time has passed
是真的  我的时代已经过去了
I am no longer relavent
我跟这时代完全没关系了
For God's sake, knock it off.
看在上帝份上  别再这么说了
I am not gonna let you feel sorry for yourself.
我不许你自己给自己泄气
- You are Tom Scavo. Damn it.
-你是汤姆·加沃斯
And?
所以呢
Sorry. I got nothing else. Come inside and eat your pork.
抱歉  没有所以  进来吧  吃猪排
This place smells funny. I don't want be here.
这里味道很怪  我不想在这呆着
Well, you should've thought about that
在你耍大牌以前
before you started acting like such a diva. Now sit down.
你就应该想到了  给我坐下
- Father Crowley!
-克劳里神父
This is a surprise.
真是稀客啊
What brings you to our soup kichten.
什么风把你吹来了
I want Juanita to work with the poor
我想让胡安妮塔和穷人一起工作
I want to teach her to be grateful
我想教她学会感恩
- for how good she has it.
-让她知道她现在环境有多好
we can always use a hand.
我们总需要帮忙
And four hands? Well, that's a blessing.
四双手呢  真是感谢
Oh, me? No, no. Not me.
我吗  不
I'm not really dressed for ladling,
我的穿着不适合舀汤
but, um, I could stand by the condiment bar
我可以站在调味台那边
and spritz people with my Chanel.
给大家喷点我的香奈儿香水
And you say Juanita is a little ungrateful? Hmm.
你是说胡安妮塔有点不知道感恩吗
Fran Schulman?
富兰.舒曼
It's Gabrielle Solis from the tennis club.
我是加布丽尔·索利斯  网球俱乐部的
Oh, of course.
哦  是你
Wow, it's been years!
那么多年过去了
The last time I saw you was at that charity fashion show.
最后一次见到你还是在慈善时尚秀上
- Wasn't that fun?
-是不是很有趣
Yes. Yes. It was.
是啊
So what are you doing here? You volunteering?
你在这做什么  当志愿者吗
- Not exactly.
-不是
Me either. My daughter is so snooty.
我也不是  我女儿太骄傲了
I am forcing her to spend time with the great unwashed.
我要让她接触接触这些下层人民
You wanna ditch this place for a cappuccino?
一起喝杯卡布奇诺吗
Actually, I am here to eat.
其实  我是来要饭的
It's Susan.
苏珊来了
Great. We don't see enough of her.
好啊  我们还没看够她
And she is not alone.
她不是一个人来的
Hey, Jackson. Long time no see. What is going on.
杰克逊  好久不见了  怎么样了
We sort of have an announcement.
我们宣布一件事
We are getting married.
我们要结婚了
Oh my God. This is such great news.
天哪  真是好消息啊
So when is the date.
什么时候
Monday.
星期一
Wow. that's kind of sudden.
这么突然
Well, when you know, you know. Why wait
时机成熟  就该行动
we are having engagement party friday you are invited.
我们在周五要办个订婚晚会  想请你们也来
A party? Count us in.
晚会吗  算上我们
I can't think of a better reason to... celebrate.
太值得庆祝了
Have you told M.J. yet?
告诉M.J.了吗
Yeah. He was on board when he found out there was cake.
是的  他发现有蛋糕的时候就知道了
Just make sure this isn't all happening too fast for him.
只是觉得对他来说  不会太突然了吧
You know kids. They need a little time to adjust.
你知道的  孩子需要一点时间来适应
Oh, kids are resilient.
孩子恢复力很强的
He'll be fine. I am just so excited.
他会没事的  我只是太高兴了
Well. I wanna you will be the first to know.
我想让你们第一个知道
We should get going. A few more neighbours to shock
我们该走了  还得去告诉别的邻居呢
We are just so happy for you.
我们替你高兴
Yeah. Congratulations.
恭喜
Now if we're going with the Damask for the settee,
如果我们用缎子做沙发面
I strongly suggest that we do the couch in the chenille.
我强烈建议做成绒布沙发
The only word I understood there was "couch."
我唯一能听懂的词就是沙发
I'll explain it to him later.
我一会儿再给他解释
Good, because they're only going to hold this fabric
好的  因为他们只打算保留这块布
For a couple of days.
就几天
Well, I am off.
好啦  我要走了
Isn't that vase divine?
这个花瓶美极了
I am so glad you like it.
我很高兴你喜欢它
I thought we were just trying out the vase.
我以为我们只是拿它来摆摆看
- I'll explain it to him later.
-我等会会跟他解释的
Okay.
好的
Thank you.
谢谢你
Can you believe this?
你相信吗
Seven years ago, Evelyn did Fran's house.
7年前  伊芙琳为富兰家负责装饰
Now? No house.
现在  她连房子都没了
That's crazy.
这太不可思议了
You ask Fran what happened?
你有没有问富兰发生了什么事
No! I didn't want to embarrass her.
没有  我不想让她难堪
You met her in line for free soup.
你在领免费汤的队伍里碰见她
How much more embarrassed could she get?
还有什么比这更尴尬的吗
Remember that dinner party she gave?
记得她以前举办地一场宴会吗
She had 20 place settings of Tiffany china.
她有20处地方放置帝梵尼陶瓷
How does this happen to someone who has Tiffany china?
一个拥有帝梵尼陶瓷的人怎么会变成这样
This is $200 a yard.
200美元一码啊
Tell Fran to save us a place in line.
告诉富兰给我们在排队时留个位
I bet I know what happened.
我知道怎么了
She drank it away.
她借酒消愁
That one New Year's Eve
除夕之夜
where she got so plowed
她心情郁闷至极
she fell in the koi pond...
掉进了酒池了
where she landed on you, drunky sue.
压在你身上  你也醉醺醺的
Everybody was hammered at that party.
那次晚会每个人都被灌醉了
Well, then it must've been a gambling problem.
那一定是赌博的问题
Based on what?
你怎么知道
She never missed bingo night at Immaculate Heart...
她一定会玩宾戈游戏
and she was Lutheran.
她是马丁·路德的信徒
You really think she bingo'ed her house away?
你真的认为她的房子是被她赌没了的
Uh, I don't know.
我不清楚
There has to be some reason.
但肯定有原因
You don't fall that far that fast
你不可能一下变得如此穷困潦倒
without making some really stupid choices.
除非做了一些愚蠢的决定
Why you gettin' so angry?
你为什么这么生气
It was Tiffany china, Carlos.
卡洛斯  帝梵尼陶瓷啊
There's the man that ruined my fishing trip.
你就是那个破坏了我钓鱼之旅的人吧
- Sorry about that, Dave.
-对不起  大卫
Oh, no worries.
不  没什么
Hey, I am so happy for you and Susan. Congratulations.
我为你和苏珊高兴  恭喜你们
Thanks.
谢谢
So how have you been?
怎么走了
We haven't had a chance to talk since...
我们还没有机会聊聊  自从
I don't know, probably the fire.
记不清了  好像是火灾之后
Uh, yeah. You were the big hero.
是的  你是个大英雄
I was the doofus that got stuck in the men's room.
我是被困在厕所里的蠢货
Oh, that was a hell of a night.
那真是可怕的一夜
Sure would like to forget that.
应该忘了它
Yeah, me, too.
对  我也这么认为
Unfortunately, I have to go down
倒霉的是  我还要去一次城里
and talk to the cops on Tuesday.
周二去跟警察谈话
Really?
真的吗
Yeah. I went down to city hall
是啊  我去市政大厅
to get my marriage certificate,
拿结婚证书
And I ran in one of the detectives from that night,
我被那晚其中一个侦探抓住了
and apparently,
很明显
They've been trying to get in touch with me.
他们一直在想办法联系我
So now I get to go down there the day after my wedding.
所以我婚后要马上去城里一趟
Some honeymoon, huh?
这也是一种蜜月
Those guys really know how to put a crimp in your day.
那些家伙真知道怎么在你的大日子里找麻烦
So did they say what they wanted to talk to you about?
那他们有说要跟你谈些什么吗
I guess they just wanna know if I saw anything suspicious.
我猜他们只是想知道  我有没有看到什么可疑的
Did you?
那你看到了吗
No.I mean, I was backstage.
没有  我当时在后台
I was headed to the men's room,
我朝着厕所跑去
and I ran into--
然后跑进去
I am so sorry.
实在是对不起
No. Don't worry about it.
不  别担心
I'll take care of it.
我来处理
I mean, there's gotta be a mop around here somewhere.
这里一定有拖把
That's not coming out.
它不会自己出现
Bree can get rid of that in a jiffy.
布里可以一下子把这处理好
Now where did she go?
她现在在哪
Okay. Showtime.
好  开始作秀
Wipe your feet first.
擦擦你的鞋
I just had the carpets cleaned.
我刚把地毯弄干净
Just because we're thieves
因为我们虽然是小偷
doesn't mean we need to be untidy.
但并不意味着我们就要脏兮兮的
Are we stealing this?
这个偷吗
Yes. As I recall, it's quite valuable.
是的  据我所知  这个很值钱
- What about this?
-这个呢
Oh, God, no.
天啊  不
That's Orson's dental Innovator of the Year award.
那是奥森的年度创新奖
I've always hated that thing.
我一直都很讨厌它
Oh, here.
那放这
What are you doing?
你在干嘛
I, uh, took some of my silver off the mantle,
我把银器拿走了
and it threw off the balance.
修复应有的平衡
Yeah.
是的
You're right. Let me help.
你说得对  我来帮你
There. Balance restored.
平衡重新恢复了
Was that necessary?
有这个必要吗
This place has to look like
这里必须看起来好像
It was ransacked by robbers,
被小偷洗劫一空的样子
not someone's personal shopper.
不是想某个人的店铺
Fine!
是的
But do you have to do it with such relish?
但是你一定要用这种方式吗
Hey, you're not paying me
你付钱给我
to just go through the motions.
不只是为了走个过场吧
Speaking of which... are you
说到这个  你
nailing Orson like we discussed?
奥森的确像你说的那样吗
That is none of your business.
这不关你事
Well, we have to make sure
是的  我们要确保
he doesn't suspect anything.
他不会产生任何怀疑
I do the bare minimum.
我所说的完全是事实
No more, no less.
毫无添油加醋
So is he just missionary?
那他是传教士吗
He seems like a strictly missionary kind of guy.
他看起来像那种严谨的传教士
Must you be so crude?
你一定要这么残忍吗
Must you always be such a priss?
你又何苦要这么较真
You freak out at the mention of sex.
一提到性你就行为异常
You never want to make a mess.
你从不会制造混乱
You suppress every spontaneous urge you ever have!
你压抑所有发自内心的欲望
Man, it must be exhausting being you!
天啊  你一定厌倦了人生
Yes, being a lady takes effort.
是的  做一个努力的女人
Well, maybe give it a rest once in a while.
是啊  也许需要休息一下
It might surprise you how good it feels.
你将会惊讶地发现  这种感觉多么好
You wanna be a Neanderthal,
你想做一个原始人
Karl? That's your choice.
卡尔  那是你的选择
I prefer to behave with class and dignity.
我选择高尚尊贵的举止
Now may we please finish robbing my home?
盗窃结束了没有
Bill Brown!
比尔·布朗
It's Tom Scavo.
我是汤姆·加沃斯
Tom! Oh, my God!
汤姆  天啊
What are you doing here?
你在这做什么
Well, Jackson and I are in the same soccer league.
杰克逊和我在同一个球队
Lynette, this is Bill Brown.
勒奈特  这是比尔·布朗
We were roommates freshmen year in college.
我们大一的时候是同宿舍的
Hi.
你好
- Really?
-真的吗
Yeah!
是的
God, you look fantastic.
天啊  你看起来很年轻
You haven't aged a day.
一点都没有变老
Hey, right back at ya.
你也一样
Liar. You didn't even recognize me.
骗人  你刚刚都没有认出我
Back up a second.
等等
You guys were classmates?
你们是同班同学吗
Yeah.
是啊
Meaning you were in the same class at the same time?
就是说你们同一时间在同一个班吗
That's what classmates means,
同班同学就是这个意思
Lynette. We're the same age.
勒奈特  我们一样大
Actually, I think I'm six months older.
事实上我比你还大6个月
You're older?!
你更大啊
I'm sorry,
不好意思
I just cannot believe...
我真是不敢相信
That they're out of stuffed mushrooms.
他们竟然从焗烤蘑菇里掉出来了
Excuse me.
不好意思
Okay, my wife's annoying,
好  我妻子是令人伤脑筋
but she is right.
但是她是对的
What's your secret?
你的年轻秘诀是什么
What is it? Diet? Exercise?
是什么  饮食  还是运动
You eatin' a bowl of stem cells every morning?
你每天早上吃一碗干细胞吗
Come on. What's going on, Peter Pan?
快点  告诉我  怎么回事  彼得.潘
Okay...You really wanna know?
好吧  你真的想知道吗
Hi!
你好啊
Aw, how sweet. Oh! And heavy.
太感谢了  好大的礼啊
Score.
真厉害
Yeah, well, we can afford to be generous
我们现在可以更慷慨一些
now that I'm off the hook for alimony.
因为以后不用给你赡养费了
Yeah. What?
对啊  什么
You're getting remarried.
你要结婚了
So I can stop sending that check every month.
我不用每月给你支票了
Everybody gets a gift.
双赢啊
Right! Score for you!
对啊  也恭喜你们
Uh, can I talk to you for a sec?
和你单独谈一下
Oh, thank you.
谢谢
You get alimony?
你有赡养费
I thought you were too proud to take alimony.
我以为你很骄傲  不会要赡养费的
I was too proud to admit it.
我很骄傲  不愿意接纳
I'm not too proud to take it.
但不代表我不去接纳
I need that money, Jackson.
我需要那些钱  杰克逊
- Well, I-I can try to chip in.-
-我会试着凑钱
"Chip in"?
凑钱
It's not a birthday cake for Shirley in accounting.
这可不是给会计部的雪莉凑钱买生日蛋糕
It's mortgage and food and insurance.
这是关于贷款  食物和保险
I'm sorry, but I can't marry you.
抱歉  我不能嫁给你
No, Susan, they'll send me back.
不  苏珊  他们会把我送回去
It's Canada, not Iran.
是加拿大啊  不是伊朗
It's like America with free health insurance.
跟美国一样啊  都有免费的医疗保险
Okay, I know this is important to you,
我知道这对你很重要
-I depend on that check every month.
-但我每个月都指望这笔钱
I know you do.
我知道
I just can't believe that I finally found a job that I love,
但我就是想不通  刚找到喜欢的工作
and now I just gotta give it up.
却又不得不放弃
Well, look, maybe... I could talk to Mike.
也许我能跟迈克谈谈
I could see if we could work something out.
看看能不能找到什么办法解决
You'd do that?
你愿意帮我吗
Yeah, I'll try.
是的  我去试试
Don't think he's not gonna want his gift back.
我觉得他不会把礼物收回
And it's really heavy, too.
这还真沉啊
So...
所以
you thought my friend bill looked pretty fantastic, huh?
你觉得我的朋友比尔看上去很棒
Okay, I went a little overboard.
我确实表现过激了
You know me--two margaritas, and I need a muzzle.
我就是这样  酒后乱说话
No, I completely agree with you. He looks really young.
不  我完全同意你  他看上去很年轻
I know, right? He must take care of himself.
我知道  他肯定很会保养
Actually, he told me his secret,
事实上  他告诉他的秘密了
and I'm thinking of doing the same thing.
我也想这么做
No, you're not having plastic surgery.
不行  你不能去做整容手术
It's my face.
这是我的脸
Uh, we live in a community property state,
我们是财产共有
so half that face is mine.
你的半个脸也是我的
Fine, you know what? You get the half below the nose.
你那半个是鼻子以下的部分
But these wrinkles up here? All going away.
这些有皱纹的部分是我的  我要把他们整掉
Tom, men don't need plastic surgery.
男人不需要整容手术  汤姆
They look better as they age.
他们越成熟越好
Real?
真的吗
Because you couldn't stop talking
因为你一直不停地说
about how great Bill looked. "you guys were classmates?
比尔看起来有多么好  你们真的是同学吗
You mean the same class at the same time?"
你说的同学是同一班吗
Okay, that's a lousy impression of me.
那是我不好
Look, Bill said it really gave him a leg up in job interviews,
比尔说这真的对他很有帮助  尤其是面试时
and I could use that right now.
我现在正用得到
You don't need a face-lift.
你不需要脸部拉皮
This is for you and Jackson.
这是给你和杰克逊的礼物
Congratulations!
恭喜你们
What if I went out and got a boob job
如果是我去做个隆胸手术
and came home with big giant sideshow boobs?
摇身一变成为超级波霸
How would you like that?
你会喜欢吗
I'd learn to live with it somehow.
我肯定会学着习惯的
You're not doing this.We can't afford it!
你不能去做  我们负担不起
It's an investment in our future. We can't afford not to.
这是为我们的将来做投资  不做才不负责任呢
I'm calling the doctor and making an appointment.
我去联系医生约个时间
If you want, I can also get a price check on a pair of--
你那一对  如果想做的话也可以去询个价
I'm not getting a boob job.
我才不会去隆胸呢
Why don't I make you a nice cup of Earl Grey...
我给你泡杯伯爵红茶如何
Oh, dear God.
天哪
Orson,we've been robbed!
奥森  我们被抢了
It wasn't me. I swear.
不是我干的  我发誓
No cuts!Back of the line.
不许加塞  后面排队去
Oh, relax. Somebody eat dinner at home...
放心  早就在自己家吃过了
in my box under the bridge.
我住桥洞底下的盒子里
Fran?
富兰
Oh, God. I was afraid I wouldn't find you here.
天哪  真担心在这儿找不到你
Ah, lucky you,I'm still poor.
算你走运  我还是这么穷
I feel bad I ducked out so fast the other day.
那天我走太急了  真抱歉
And I've been thinking about you a lot,
后来我一直在想你的事
and I just...I really wanna help.
真的很想帮你
Wow.Thank you. Thank you!
谢谢你  谢谢你
Now...I just wanna make sure
我只是想确认下
that you're not gonna...you know...
你会是在  这样吧[喝酒的手势]
Drinking was nevermy problem, Gaby.
加布  我从来不酗酒的
I didn't think so.You were always so classy.
我不这么认为  你以前多漂亮啊
20, 40, 60...Was it drugs?
20  40  60  那是因为嗑药吗
No. I never did drugs.
不  我从没嗑过药
Good to know.80, 100.
那好  80  100
Because gambling is bad enough without being high.
因为赌博更不好  更易沉迷
I never gambled a day in my life, Gaby.
我这辈子从来没赌过  加布
Well, then what the hell happened?
那到底发生了什么事
This doesn't make sense.
这根本说不通呀
I was at your house.You had such lovely things.
我去过你家  看到过你富足快乐的生活
Yes, Mark and I lived really well.
是的  那时候我和马克过得很好
Probably a little...too well.
可能是有点太好了吧
But we were young,
我们挥霍青春
and we thought we had time to save for the future.
却觉得未来尽在掌握
Then he died.
然后  他死了
Mark died?I didn't know.
马克死了  我都不知道
He was sick a really long time.
他一病不起
He couldn't work.He lost his insurance.
没法工作  没有保险
By the time he passed away
到他去世的时候
we were completely wiped out.
我们已经一贫如洗了
Oh, Fran, I'm so sorry.
富兰  太遗憾了
You didn't have any family to turn to? Any friends?
你们没有什么家人可以投靠吗  朋友呢
No family,and it turns out not too many friends either.
没有家人  到最后也没多少朋友了
Look Gaby I know you came here wanting to
加布  我知道你过来是想弄清楚
find out what I did to make this all happen.
我到底做了什么落得如此下场
But the truth is, we're all just an accident or a tumor
事实是  一次事故  一场疾病或者一次投资失败
or a bad investment away from...
就足以把我们打回原形
standing in line for free soup.
沦落到排队领救济餐的境地
Thank you.
谢谢你
I don't agree, Fran.
我不同意你的说法  富兰
You know, Carlos went blind for five years.
卡洛斯曾经失明整整5年
We went broke.We almost lost our house.
我们破产了  一度穷到几乎无家可归
But we worked our asses off and we made it back.
但我们照样努力工作终于挽回了败局
Oh, so just because you survived that,
所以  你觉得你已经度过了那个难关
you think you've crossed some kind of finish line,
以后就苦尽甘来一帆风顺了
that nothing bad can happen again?
再也不会一夜回到解放前了
- Well, no, but...
-不  但是
Listen.
听我说
I hope it works out for you.
我希望你能如愿以偿
I hope you never lose that big, beautiful home of yours.
希望你永远不会失去你的大家庭
God knows I wish I'd appreciated mine more while I had it.
如果我能回到从前  我一定会倍加珍惜
Thank you again.
再次谢谢你
Remind me again when you're getting your teeth cleaned.
你什么时候去洗牙  到时候再提醒我一下
Um... the 14th.
14号
And the 15th, we have tickets
你一直想拉我去看的那部戏 15号的
to that play that you're dragging me to.
我们有票  可以去看了
Yes. Why?
好的  为什么说起这些
I'm just--I'm trying to figure out
只是确认下
when would be a good time to get married.
哪天会是个结婚的好日子
I'm sorry.What did you just...
抱歉  你刚刚这是在
I know, I know.
我知道我知道
Not the most romantic proposal in the world.
肯定算不上世界上最浪漫的求婚方式
I shouldn't have led with the teeth cleaning.
真不该以洗牙这样的谈话开始
I feel I can overlook that.
我觉得这点我可以忽略掉
So is that a yes?
这么说你答应了
Yes! It's a yes!
是的  我答应了
Wow! What brought this on?
为什么突然提起这个
It just seemed like the right time.
只是觉得时机到了
Oh, Mike. I'm so happy.
麦克  我太高兴了
I love you.
我爱你
I love you, too.
我也爱你
I understand taking things,
我能理解他们抢走了东西
but why smash something you're gonna leave behind?
但为什么要弄坏这些带不走的东西呢
They're robbers,dear. Not personal shoppers.
亲爱的  他们是强盗  可不是来购物的
Yeah, well, whoever did this should be shot.
不管是谁  干这事的真该被枪毙
Well, I wonder if the victims of your kleptomania
我在想那些被你光顾过的失主
felt the same way.
是不是也这么想
You know what?You're absolutely right.
知道吗  你说得太对了
I never realized what my stealing put people through.
我从来没意识到我的盗窃癖对别人造成的影响
Maybe this is karma.
也许这就是报应吧
What is that?
那是什么
It's a picture of the mask they stole.
他们偷去的一个面具的图
I drew it from memory.
我照着记忆画下来的
Remember where we got it?
还记得我们在哪买的吗
Was it Florence?
佛罗伦萨吗
Venice.
是威尼斯
We walked past that little shop under the bridge,
我们在桥下散步的时候经过一家小店
and you saw it in the window.
透过窗户  你看见了这个
Oh, that's right.
是啊
You told me you'd been wearing a mask all your life,
你跟我说过你的一生都戴着面具而活
but with me, you felt--
但跟我在一起  你觉得
Like I could finally take it off and be myself.
我终于可以脱下面具  做回自己了
Yeah.Anyway, I faxed itto the shop in Venice.
是的  总之我给威尼斯的那家店发了个传真
They said they could make a new one.
他们说可以再做一个新的
I should have it for you in about a month.
一个月左右就可以到你手上了
I can't believe you went to all that trouble
真不敢相信你为我做了这么多
No, of course not. What's on your mind?
不会  不打扰  有什么事吗
Well, I figured it was time to get back to work,
我觉得是时候回去工作了
so I put together a speaking tour--
所以定了个演讲行程
Seattle, Portland,my usual route.
我的惯驶航线是西雅图到波特兰
Work? Are you sure it's not too soon?
工作  你确定不会太赶了点
Well, I have to do it eventually.
总得冒险一试才行啊
Anyway, I was hoping
不管怎样  希望你能答应
you could check in on the house now and then.
时不时地帮我照看下屋子
Of course.
当然可以
Someone's at my door.Let me get rid of them.
有人敲门  我先打发了再说
Hey, Katherine,is Mike here?
凯瑟琳  麦克在吗
- No, he's at work.
-不在  他在上班
Oh, shoot. Um...
糟糕
Can you tell him to call me as soon as he gets back?
你能转告他一回来就打电话给我好吗
Sure.Is everything okay?
当然  你还好吧
Uh, well...
其实
Okay, Mike's probably gonna tell you anyway,
麦克肯定会告诉你的
so just can't tell anyone else, okay?
但你千万别告诉别人  好吗
There's not a problem with the wedding, is there?
不是婚礼出问题了吧
It's still on, right?
会如期举行吧
It depends.
难说
Jackson and I are only getting married
杰克逊和我结婚
because he needs his green card.
仅仅是为了他的绿卡
And then I realized that I would lose my alimony.
后来发现我会失去赡养费
So unless Mike will keep paying me, I can't get married.
除非麦克继续给钱  不然我不能结婚
You have to.
必须结
I mean, poor Jackson.
杰克逊多可怜啊
I-I would hate to see him deported back to...
不想看到他被遣送回
- Where's he from?
-他从哪来的
Canada.
加拿大
Oh! Oh! Brr! We can't have that!
不能让这种事情发生
If you want, I could talk to Mike for you.
那要不我转告麦克吧
That would be great.
太好了
Just tell him I need answer quickly, the wedding is monday
告诉他尽快答复  因为婚礼是下周一
don't cancel anything yet. You'll have your answer tonight.
别急着取消啊  今晚就答复你
Thanks.
谢谢
Sorry, Dave.
抱歉  大卫
Dave?
大卫
Hey, Lynette. How's it going?
勒奈特  别来无恙吧
my husband wants to spend money we don't have
我老公想预支钱做不必要的整容
on a face-lift he doesn't need, so... not great.
所以不怎么好
Mm, tell him to be careful.
告诉他小心点
Have you seen Bruce in payroll?
你见过工资单上的布鲁斯吗
He just went in for a little nip and tuck.
他刚去做了整容手术
And? How's he look?
然后呢  怎样了
Like he's standing in a wind tunnel.
他像站在风洞里一样
Really?
是吗
Poor Bruce.
可怜的布鲁斯
What's his extension?
他是哪个部门的
And I'm thinking I may have acted rashly.
我觉得还是太草率了
I mean, every marriage has its rough patches.
没有婚姻是完美的
Orson loves me, and deep down, he's a good man.
奥森爱我  其实他也是个好人
If I stick with this, maybe we can make it work.
如果我坚持下去  也许能过下去
Are you even listening to me?
你到底有没有在听啊
Don't need to. Heard it all before.
没必要  早听过了
Oh, really?
是吗
I've been doing this 20 years.
我干这行都20年了
And trust me,
相信我
every woman gets cold feet.
每个女人都会心软
"Am I making a mistake?"
我是不是做错了
"Was he really that bad?"
他真的那么坏吗
"Maybe I could try harder."
也许我能再努力些
And I'm gonna tell you what I tell them--
我会告诉你相同的话
you're  not making a mistake.
你没有做错
He really is that bad.
他就是有那么坏
And no matter how hard you try,
不管你多努力
he's still gonna be the same jerk
他还是那个最开始
who sent you into this office in the first place.
让你走进这间办公室的人
Oh. So I'm just like everyone else,
所以我和其他人一样
and you know everything I'm going to say.
我要说什么你都知道
I even know the stuff you're not going to say.
我还知道你不会的话
I doubt that.
我不信
Let me give it a shot.
那我试试
You've been thinking,
你一直在想
"What happens if I walk away from Orson
如果我离开奥森  放弃为这段感情
and everything I invested in this relationship?"
付出的一切  会怎么样呢
"Will I ever find another man?"
我还能找到新的归宿吗
Will you spend the rest of your life alone?
你会孤独一生吗
Close?
差不多吧
In the ballpark.
差不离
Well, you listen to me.
你听我说
You've got nothing to worry about.
你没什么好担心的
You're a beautiful, elegant, classy woman,
你是个美丽  优雅  高贵的女人
and there's no way you're gonna end up alone.
不可能会孤老终身
And do you say that to every woman, too?
你也对每个女人这么说吗
I mean, I get some real uggos in here.
我真接待过些老女人
You know, the kind that are gonna die alone
那些要孤独死去
and get eaten by their cats.
被自己猫啃噬的人
Charming.
厉害啊
So are we back in business?
能继续谈正事了吗
Send me the papers when they're ready.
文件好了就给我送来
Honey, I'm glad you're home.
亲爱的  你终于回来了
I brought someone me from work I want you to meet.
我有同事要给你介绍
Yeah. It turns out he got the same procedure
他做了
that you're thinking about getting.
你想做的那种手术
So I thought maybe you could chat him up about it.
我想你们可以聊聊
So you're finally on board with this?
你最终还是同意我了
Well, like you said, it's your face.
如你所说  是你自己的脸嘛
Come on, I'm dying for you to meet Bruce.
快点  我就想让你见见布鲁斯
Bruce, I want you to meet my husband Tom.
布鲁斯  给你介绍我老公汤姆
Tom, this is Bruce
汤姆  这是布鲁斯
Hi, Tom.
你好  汤姆
So, um, Lynette tells me
勒奈特告诉我
you're thinking about having a little elective surgery.
你准备做选择性手术
Did she?
她说了啊
Now you may not be able to tell,
也许你现在看不出来
but I've had work done.
我的手术已经完成了
Really? Have they finished?
是吗  他们完成了吗
Now I should warn you that, uh...
我应该给你个警告
after they operate, it looks a little weird.
做完手术后  看起来有点诡异
Oh, I was wondering about that. Yeah.
我正觉得奇怪呢
But eventually it settles, like this.
但最后还是解决了  就是这样
Isn't it exciting, Tom?
是不是很兴奋啊  汤姆
In a few weeks, you are gonna look just like Bruce.
再过几周  你就和布鲁斯长得一样了
Hey, if you want, I'll give you the name of my surgeon.
如果你想要  我把我的主治医生告诉你
Yes. I definitely want the name of the guy who did that.
好啊  我要知道是谁做的
Lynette, Bruce looks like he could use something to drink,
勒奈特  布鲁斯好像想喝东西
and I know that I sure could.
我肯定能办到
C-could you excuse us for a sec?
抱歉  我们离开一下
Very clever, Lynette--inviting the joker over to scare me.
真聪明啊  勒奈特  弄个小丑过来吓我
I wanted you to see the face they don't put in the brochure.
我想让你看看宣传册中没有的脸
I will be having my work done by a reputable surgeon.
我会让著名医生来主刀
Bruce looks like his was done by a bear.
布鲁斯就好像是熊给他开刀的
That's my point.
这就是我想说的
You don't know how these things will turn out.
你不知道结果会是怎样
Well, I am willing to take that risk. I'm doing it.
我愿意承担风险  我就是要做
Why are you being so stubborn?
你干嘛这么顽固
Why do you care so much?
你干嘛管这么多
Because I don't want to have plastic surgery.
因为我不想整容
What?
什么
Tom, if you're unsatisfied with your looks,
汤姆  如果你不满意自己的相貌
someday you're gonna be unsatisfied with mine.
总有一天你也会对我厌倦的
- No.
-不会的
Yes.
会的
You're going to look me someday with your brand-new face
某一天你会用崭新的脸看着我
And say, "when did she get so old?"
然后说  她什么时候这么老了
We won't look like we belong together anymore.
我们不再会比翼双飞了
Lynette, I'm just talking about gettin' rid of a few wrinkles.
勒奈特  我只是想磨平一点皱纹
But I don't see your wrinkles, Tom.
我没看到皱纹啊  汤姆
I see our whole life together.
我看到的是我们走过的岁月
This...
这是
is you worrying about how you're going to provide for us.
你在思考如何养活我们
This is Penny falling out of the tree house
这是佩妮从树屋上掉下来
and breaking her arm.
摔断了手臂
This is my cancer.
这是我的癌症
These are the millions of laughs
这是让我们挺过
that got us through all those tough times.
艰难时期的笑容
It's like a map of our marriage,
就像是我们婚姻的轨迹
and I don't want to lose it.
我不想失去它
And it if keeps me from getting a job?
如果因此我不能找到工作呢
You're gonna get a job,
你会找到工作的
And it'll be because they're impressed by your experience,
是因为你有丰富的经验
not your wrinkle-free face.
而不是光滑的皮肤
I know exactly what you mean.
我完全了解你的意思了
And I love your face, too.
我也爱你的脸蛋
And this wrinkle here, that's when--
这里的皱纹  是在
This isn't about me, Tom.
现在不是说我  汤姆
Come on.
走吧
Talked to Katherine. You'll get your alimony.  Mike.
和凯瑟琳谈过了  赡养费照旧  麦克
Hey. Good news.
好消息
Mike agreed to keep paying me alimony. He sent me a text.
麦克传简讯给我  他同意继续付赡养费
Oh, man. That's a relief.
太好了  我可以松一口气了
And unbelievably generous.
他太大方了
I'm gonna send him a thank-you right now.
我得对他说一声谢谢
(Mike, thank you thank you thank you…..SO MUCH!!!!!)
麦克  真的是太太太感谢你了
You're welcome.
不客气
You know, I really can't tell you
苏珊  我真的不知道
how much I appreciate you doing this for me, Susan.
该如何来表达对你的感谢
And I promise,as long as I'm here,
我保证  只要我在这里
I'll pitch in around the house, run errands.
我有什么需要我做的  我一定随叫随到
You know, just like a real husband.
就像真正的丈夫一样
Clearly, you've never been married before.
显然你没有结过婚
Well, you know, just because this is, um...
我想说  可能正是一个冒牌婚姻
a fake marriage, doesn't mean it can't be wonderful.
会出现许多让人意想不到的惊喜呢
Well, I've been in some real marriages that weren't,
我经历过真正的婚姻
so... maybe you're right.
所以我认为  你可能是对的
Oh, look. Cans.
看看  易拉罐
You can't have a wedding without cans and signage!
婚礼离不开易拉罐和结婚标志
Sweet!
太贴心了
Let's get to the car wash on our way to the courthouse.
我们去法院的路上先把车洗了
Jackson Braddock?
杰克逊.布拉多克
Yes?
什么事
We're with immigration.
我们是移民局的
You're in the country on an expired visa.
你持有过期签证
- You're gonna have to come with us.
-你得跟我们走一趟
Oh, no, no, no.
不行  不
- you can't take him now.
-你们不能带他走
Mam, I need you to step back.
女士  请退后
Susan, there's a business card on the dresser
苏珊  化妆台上有一张律师的名片
with an attorney's number.  call him for me, please?
请帮我打给他
Please, can't this wait? We're about to get married.
我们能等等吗  我们马上就结婚了
Not today you're not.
你们选错日子了
What's going on? Who are these guys?
发生什么事了  他们是谁
immigration agents, and I think they're...
移民局的  我想
sending Jackson back to Canada.
她们要把杰克逊遣送回加拿大
Hello?
你好
May I speak with, uh, Bree Van de Kamp?
请找布里·范德坎普
Oh, she's not in at the moment. Can I take a message?
她现在不在  请留言
Uh, yeah, this is Sheila with Weston Brothers Storage.
我是威斯顿兄弟仓库的西拉
It's about the storage unit she just rented.
我想谈谈关于她租的存储间
Storage unit?
存储间
Uh, yeah, we overcharged her on the deposit.
对  我们的保证金多算了
Tell her not to worry.
告诉她不用担心
We're gonna deduct it from her next bill.
我们会在她下张订单里扣除掉的
- Okay. Uh, thank you.
-好的  谢谢
You're welcome.
不客气
Everyone wears some kind of mask,
每个人都戴着面具
so you must look closely
你必须睁大双眼
to find the truth that lies beneath.
才能发现谎言后的真相
Some conceal anxiety about growing older.
有人掩饰年华逝去的恐惧
Some hide fears of financial ruin.
有人隐藏对于破产的畏惧
Others cover up a love that continues to linger.
有人将无法忘去的真爱掩埋
And then there are those who let their masks slip.
有些人的面具不小心滑落
If you look to their eyes,
如果你仔细看着他们的双眸
you'll see who they really are...
他们才会现出原形
及其精心盘算的计划
and exactly what they're capable of.